jobinventory.com 2011-12-17

# Privacy Policy // JobInventory.com

**General**

This website is exclusively owned and operated under the name “JobInventory.com” by Buzz Vertical, LLC, a Delaware Limited Liability Company. This privacy policy defines the treatment of personally identifiable information that Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com collects when you are on the Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com website, and when you use Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com’s services. This policy also covers Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com’s treatment of any personally identifiable information that Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com’s business partners share with Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com or that Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com may collect on a partner's site. This policy does __not__ apply to the practices of companies that Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com does not own or control or to people that Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection**

Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com will be the sole owner of all information collected on this site. Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com collects personally identifiable information when: 

  * You register for an account with this website;
  * You visit pages within the Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com website;
  * You submit questions or other requests for information or comments to the website;
  * You use certain Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com products or services, including when you subscribe to one or more of our newsletters, participate in surveys or contests run through the site or utilize our message boards to discuss common issues with other registered site users;
  * You transact business with our affiliates or business partners; and
  * We access publicly available information from public suppliers of such information, including, but not limited to, government agencies and consumer reporting agencies, to assist in the enforcement and monitoring of your transactions. This may include aggregate labor statistics obtained from government agencies, none of which will contain personally identifying information about you. We use this aggregated information to better serve you by analyzing the employment market, engaging in site administration and gathering general demographic information. This aggregated, non-personal information may be shared with third parties, including advertisers;
  * We send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identify your browser. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Please note: 
    * We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by:
      * Storing user preferences;
      * Tracking user trends and activity, including, specifically, how you arrived at our site;
      * Allowing you to change pages during your site visit without having to re-enter your user name and password; and
      * Delivering information specific to your needs and interests. 
    * Other companies, including, but not limited to, those which advertise on our site, may use cookies to identify your computer when sending you an advertisement. These cookies may be used to compile information about you and others who use your computer, including, but not limited to, your physical location, the websites and subject matter which you have accessed and read and which advertisements you have reviewed or followed to another site. This information is used to target future advertisements to you. We have no access to or control over other companies' use of cookies and their use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one; 
    * Some features and services of Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com or other sites may not function properly if your cookies are disabled; and
    * To request changes to or deletion of your own Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com account, and to read about what information may possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted email us at contact@JobInventory.com.

Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com may collect the following types of information:

  * Information which personally identifies you and which may include, but is not limited to, your name, username, email address, physical address, zip code, phone, age, gender information, annual income, employment information and fax numbers;
  * Personal financial information which may include, but is not limited to, your secure credit card information, your bank account information (including account number and routing number), and the amount of money in your bank account; 
  * Information about the domain and the host from which you access our services, including the computer's Internet address and the browser and other software in use; 
  * Demographic information which may include, but is not limited to, your age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites; and
  * Information about your individual or aggregated transactions through our system or those of our affiliates and business partners which may include information about persons to whom you have sent money and from whom you have received money

Information which is required for access to the site and participation in site services or activities will be identified as required; information which is optional will be identified as optional. Some of this information, such as your name, username and/or E-mail address, among other information, may be available to other registered users of the site. 

Prior to providing Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com with information, you will be offered a link that allows you to review this privacy policy and you will be provided with an opportunity to "opt out" of the collection of certain information and of certain uses of your personal information, when applicable. If you do not "opt out" of the collection and use of information you are consenting to the collection, transfer and storage of the information, including the possible transfer and storage of that information outside the country where you reside or access this Web Site. You should consult with your local country's privacy laws for more information. 

Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com fully complies with all requirements of the Child Online Privacy Protection Act. 

**Information Use**

Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com uses information for several purposes, including, but not limited to: 

  * Verifying your identity;
  * Collecting and distributing payments;
  * Detecting and preventing fraud and other illegal uses of our service;
  * Fulfilling your requests for certain products and services; 
  * Contacting you about new products, surveys, and, in the event they are held, to tell you that you have won a contest or other promotional prize 
  * Engaging in research that will improve this site and those of our partners; and
  * Improving site administration and functioning and our overall services to you; 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com may also send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people in certain circumstances, including when we: 

  * Have your permission to share the information such as: 
    * Companies with whom we affiliate; 
    * Advertising and direct marketing companies; and
    * Institutions, financial and otherwise, with whom we share marketing agreements.
  * Need to share your information with the business partners or affiliates who assist us in providing requested services to you, which include, but are not limited to, financial service providers, banks, credit card companies, and brokerage houses, and companies with whom we plan to merge with or be acquired by;
  * From time to time, offer you the opportunity to post or otherwise provide your resume and personal information to specific employers or other partner organizations or sites. We will only disclose such information to specific authorized employers, organizations or sites, though you should assume that this information will be used to contact you with regard to any manner of topics which may or may not be limited to employment opportunities and that it will be posted publicly by the employers, organizations or sites. Once your information is given to a third party employer, organization or site, that employer's, organization's or site's privacy policy is controlling with regard to the information provided and you must contact that employer, organization or site with any questions, comments or requests pertaining to your information;
  * Respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process or other formal requests issued by a government office or agency; and
  * Have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: 
    * Protect and defend the rights or property of Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com; 
    * Act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com, or the public; or 
    * Enforce violations of the Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com User Agreement or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services 

Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com may share aggregated, non-personal data and information with media partners, professionals and advertisers. 

**Security**

Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com endeavors to maintain the requisite security to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure both on and offline at a level that is equal to or better than that which is required by applicable law. Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure from anyone other than our employees, agents, representatives, business partners and affiliates. When personal information or personal financial information is transmitted to other Web Sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, in this case the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol and requires the use of a password with the following protections: 

  * The password will itself be encrypted and stored in our protected database for security purposes; 

  * The password will be required to be greater than 8 characters long to enhance security

Please understand that, despite our best efforts, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions on the Internet which may compromise your personal information. 

**Correcting your Personal Information**

**Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com** asks that you provide us with any changes to your personal information or your privacy preferences so that we can update your account accordingly. **Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com** is not responsible for any notifications or updates that do not reach you because you have not notified **Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com** of changes to your contact information. 

Changes should be sent to **contact@JobInventory.com.** We will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before making corrections. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Buzz Vertical, LLC/JobInventory.com is protecting your information.
